playseat.com 2012-06-13

# Privacy | playseats

Ordering Playseats products Online is designed to be as simple as possible, while allowing maximum security and privacy for all your details.

### ENCRYPTION

Crucially, unencrypted credit card details will not be stored on our server, and will be sent only in encrypted form. The encryption technologies we use are SSL and PGP.

For more information about these technologies see, [http://www.pgp.com](http://www.pgp.com/) for information about PGP and, [http://info.ssl.com](http://info.ssl.com/article.aspx?id=10241) for more information about SSL.

### COLLECTING ANONYMOUS INFORMATION

We automatically collect general website traffic information (such as how many people have visited the site, most popular pages etc). This information is collected into aggregate results in order to evaluate our service and business practice in an effort to provide you with an optimum shopping service.

We may share non-personal, aggregated information with other Playseats Divisions, our partners or product distributors for research purposes. We will never identify or disclose individual customers or visitors information or purchases but may disclose how many customers bought a specific item or used a specific service such as am email list.

### COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION

We collect personal information submitted by you to manage and deliver your order or as part of an entry to a competition or product review. We do not disclose personal information for any other purpose.

### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will use personal information as supplied by you to process and deliver your order. We will disclose personal information such as your delivery address to a delivery service provider (ie a courier) as selected by you when you place your order. We also retain your order details in a secure offline system that is NOT connected to the internet. This is so we have a record of your order should you wish to return or exchange an item at a later date.

Under no circumstances will Playseats Online sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.

### COOKIES

For added convenience, we have employed a “cookie” system for our website. A “cookie” is a small file placed on a customer’s machine which lets our site store information. This information allows us to make our site easier to use. Cookies allow our servers to keep track of customer details between visits to our site. The information stored by the cookie includes the data that is provided during online registration. This information is only accessible online when a customer enters their username and password. Other information stored by the cookie includes website traffic data. This is not used to identify individual details but only collated into aggregate anonymous results in order to evaluate and improve our shopping service for our customers.

Credit card information is never stored in the cookie.

### PRIVACY

Personal information like address, phone etc is only accessible after supplying a username and password. You must login before you can check your Order Status, View/Edit their Registration details, order Online.

Once you have logged in your account will remain open until you quit the browser.

### EMAIL ADDRESSES

We will store your email address if you: send us a query; place an order or subscribe to an email list. Your email addresses is used for the purpose you provide it for and statistical information.

They are never disclosed for any other purpose.

### SPAM

We will never knowingly send you electronic messages without your consent. For more information on the ‘Spam Act 2003′ please visit the Australian Government’s website:  
<http://www.dcita.gov.au/communications_and_technology/policy_and_legislation/spam>

### CREDIT CARD

Unencrypted credit card information is NOT stored on our internet servers. When you place an order our website encrypts and passes all order information to our back-office system. This system is not connected directly to the internet.

### THIRD PARTIES

The Playseats Shop never sells personal or anonymous information to third parties. Our business arrangements with third party service providers provide for complete confidentiality and adhere to the ABC’s Editorial Policy.

### FEEDBACK AND COMPLAINTS HANDLING PROCEDURE

The Playseats Shop welcomes feedback and attends to all complaints promptly. Please write to us using the contact information presented on this page http://www.playseat.com/shop/index.php/contacts.

### PEACE OF MIND

We will only use your details and order information, including mailing addresses, email address, and phone number, to fulfill your order and to advise of the status of the order.
